Guide to the David Richmond Gergen Papers, 1964-1999 (bulk 1971-1992) RL.00443
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2000-0415)
  - SR 21-D. Gergen1991 May 15 (Box 14)
    - Oxford Debates (Box 14)
    - Thank you [to Gergen]-1989 (Box 14)
    - Newsletters, 1990, 4 folders and continued in box 15 (Box 14)
  - SR 31 continued from box 13 (Box 15)
    - Defense Monitor,1990 (Box 15)
    - Evans-Novak,1990 (Box 15)
    - Governor's Bulletin,1990 (Box 15)
    - Janeway Letter,1990 (Box 15)
    - Georgetown Leadership Seminar (Box 15)
    - Bush's Cabinet,1988
      - Personnel (Box 15)
      - Cheney (Box 15)
      - Fordites in the Cabinet (Box 15)
      - James Baker - Secretary of State (Box 15)
      - John Tower, 1988, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Sam Skinner - Transportation (Box 15)
      - Transition (Box 15)
      - Ronald Reagan (Box 15)
      - Mosbacher (Box 15)
      - Ann Novick - USIA - faxes (Box 15)
      - IMF/World Bank (Box 15)
      - William Bennett (Box 15)
    - American Assembly, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Budget
      - Budget Issues/Unmet Needs (Box 15)
      - Capital Gains (Box 15)
      - Deficits (Box 15)
      - Gramm Rudmann,1988 (Box 15)
      - NAM Budget Game,1988 (Box 15)
      - Consortia/Capital (Box 15)
      - The Dollar (Box 15)
      - Bush's Budget, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Military (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency
      - This Honorable Court (Box 15)
      - 19th Annual Symposium (Box 15)
      - The President in Transition (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - AEI
      - Adweek (Box 15)
      - Annual Report,1987 (Box 15)
      - Francis Boyer Lecture (Box 15)
      - Minimum Wage (Box 15)
    - Chase Manhattan
      - Speech,1988 November 29 (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - Bush 100 Days, 4 folders (Box 15)
  - SR 30 continued from box 7 (Box 16)
    - Environment, folder 3 of 3 (Box 16)
    - ICI/IBCC (Box 16)
    - WPA (Box 16)
    - The Future of the U.S.-Japan Relationship (Box 16)
    - International News and the American Media (Box 16)
    - Foreign Direct Investment: Net Economic Benefits and Political Risks (Box 16)
    - The Right to Choose: Public School Choice and the Future of American Education (Box 16)
    - Foreign Policy Experts (Box 16)
    - CSIS:
      - DG CSIS (Hostage) (Box 16)
      - CSIS: Foreign Policy and Media, CSIS paper,1998 December 1, Joe Fromm (Box 16)
      - US News and World Report folder [foreign policy material] (Box 16)
  - Info. Files [Q-T] (Box 16)
    - Quinnipac College (Box 16)
    - RJR Nabisco: Gertsner (Box 16)
    - RNC--Rep. Nat'l Comm. (Box 16)
    - Rockefeller Found. (Box 16)
    - Roper Center (Box 16)
    - Russell Reynolds (Box 16)
    - Russia (Box 16)
    - RWJ Found./Health Care (Box 16)
    - RWJ Foundation (Box 16)
    - Savings and Investments (Box 16)
    - Savings and Loans (Box 16)
    - SDI (Box 16)
    - Semiconductors (Box 16)
    - Senate Armed Services Hearings, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Sexual Harassment--Congress (Box 16)
    - Skills (Box 16)
    - Smithsonian Council, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Soviet Affairs (Box 16)
    - Soviet Relations--American Comm. (Box 16)
    - Spina Bifida (Box 16)
    - SRI International (Box 16)
    - Student Aid (Box 16)
    - Student Aid (Box 16)
    - Superfund (Box 16)
    - Surdna Foundation (Box 16)
    - Tabloid Journalism (Box 16)
    - Taxes (Box 16)
    - Technology Policy (Box 16)
    - Term Limitations, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Terrorism (Box 16)
    - Thank You Notes, folders 1 and 2 of 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Info. Files [Q-T], continued (Box 17)
    - Thank You Notes, folder 3 of 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Thomas Hearings, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Tobacco Issues/Pol. Camps. (Box 17)
    - Transportation (Box 17)
    - Trilateral Commission (Box 17)
    - (4 folders) (Box 17)
    - UNCW--Strategy Council (Box 17)
    - Unemployment/Family Leave (Box 17)
    - United Kingdom (Box 17)
    - United Nations (Box 17)
    - Union Carbide (Box 17)
    - University of Maryland--Public Affairs, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - [Box #12, No SR number]--White House Documents; Baldwin Wallace College; Citation, Cape (Box 17)
    - Kitfield/Military Reform, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Tina Rosenberg:The Haunted Land (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 17)
    - [Unfoldered material:People article on Gergen and White House Security memo] (Box 17)
    - Call SheetsMay 31-June 4 (Box 17)
    - Current Phone Logs (Box 17)
    - Book Publisher Catalogs (Box 17)
    - Chase:In a Dark Wood, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Bill Gates:The Road Ahead, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Evan Thomas (Box 17)
    - Reed/Religion and Press and Politics (Box 17)
  - [Box #12], continued (Box 18)
    - Election1990, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Phone Logs,1990 November-1991 March, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Clinton's Plan - Issues Campaign,1992 (Box 18)
    - White Myths about Blacks (Box 18)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - People
      - Madeline Albright, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Les Aspin, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Bruce Babbitt, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Zoe Baird, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Lloyd Bentsen (Box 18)
      - Jesse Brown, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Ron Brown (Box 18)
      - Carol Browner, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Warren Christopher, 4 folders (Box 18)
      - Henry Cisneros, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Mike Espy, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Kantor (Box 18)
      - Thomas Mack McLarty, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Magaziner (Box 18)
      - Hazel O'Leary, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Federico Pena (Box 18)
      - Richard Reich, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Richard Riley, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Robert Rubin, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Donna Shalala - HHS, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Laura Tyson, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - James Woolsey (Box 18)
      - Gore (Box 18)
        [legal folder]
  - SR 14 (Box 18)
    - Press. Politics. Public Policy (Box 18)
    - Peru (Box 18)
    - Polls, 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Transition Speed (Box 18)
      [this material plus last two folders in box 11 appear to be different from the rest of SR 14]
  - SR 14, continued (Box 19)
    - Points of Light (Box 19)
    - Markle Commission (several bound items) (Box 19)
    - Japan, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Job Skills (Box 19)
    - The Kamber Group (Box 19)
    - Kenya (Box 19)
    - Labor (Box 19)
    - US - Law/Crime (Box 19)
    - Leadership (Box 19)
    - Legal Reform (Box 19)
    - Lisbeth Schorr (Box 19)
    - London - G7 Summit (Box 19)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer: Show Copies,1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Market Strategies: AM Talk Issues Foundation (Box 19)
    - Marjorie Williams Piece (Box 19)
    - Center for Media and Public Affairs (Box 19)
    - Mexico - US Trade (Box 19)
    - Mideast Peace Conference (Box 19)
    - MIL Convention, 1992 (Box 19)
    - Military Reductions (Box 19)
    - Monitor Channel (Box 19)
    - NATO (Box 19)
    - Nat'l Comm - US/China Relations (Box 19)
    - National Endow. Humanities (Box 19)
    - Northeast Asian Security (Box 19)
    - Nuclear Weapons (Box 19)
    - NYNEX (Box 19)
    - Communications Industry Forecast (Box 19)
    - Population Growth (Box 19)
  - [Diana] Pierce #17, Old Resumes, Old Financial Statements, Files off Desk (X-Mas Cards, Etc.), Spk. Eng. Poss. (Right-Hand Side Stuff) (Box 20)
    - Correspondence
      - Conferences, speaking engagements, etc. (Box 20)
      - Invitations, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Information on DYG, Inc. (Box 20)
    - Old Resumes
      - Smith, Nancy1993 (Box 20)
      - Thompson, Wendy1993 (Box 20)
      - Job Applicants, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - [Job Applicants] who didn't make the second cut (Box 20)
      - No's 52 [Rejected job applicants], 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Not possibles 68 [Rejected job applicants], 2 folders (Box 20)
      - No's 49 [Rejected job applicants], 2 folders (Box 20)
    - DRG RS-452 (Box 20)
    - Loose Material, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Notes on Ross Perot (Box 20)
    - Dianna1992 March 19-1992 March 31 (Box 20)
    - Mail for DG's attention (Box 20)
    - Regrets March 26 on (Box 20)
    - Misc. (Box 20)
    - Crisis management/press (Box 20)
    - Morita, Akio, contains 2 audio tapes (Box 20)
    - Reading material (Box 20)
    - DG mail: weekly lists (Box 20)
    - Recommendations, Jodi Newcombe (Box 20)
    - Resumes,1992 (Box 20)
    - 1991 Expenses Reimb. (Box 20)
    - 1992 Expenses Reimb., 2 folders (Box 20)
  - SR 29-Info. Files (Box 21)
    - China (Box 21)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour Press Information, includes 6 photographs (Box 21)
    - [Sea Pines, SC] (Box 21)
      [Material inside the Sea Pines folder may not be related to folder title]
    - Certificate of Appreciation from Treasury Executive Institute,1990 (Box 21)
    - Press, 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Public Radio contract (Box 21)
    - Political Advertising (Box 21)
    - Political Anger (Box 21)
    - Policy Perspectives (Box 21)
    - Poland and Emergency Aid to Poland, 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Politics,1990 (Box 21)
    - Portugal (Box 21)
    - Presidency, 3 folders (Box 21)
      Including Presidential Campaign,1992 and Presidential Debates
    - Polls and Public Opinion (11) (Box 21)
      Including opinions on public policy and racial problems
  - SR 29, continued (Box 22)
    - Science Investment (Box 22)
    - Polls, 5 folders (Box 22)
  - Pierce #17, continued (Box 22)
    - Photos to Send/Sign, includes 2 photographs (Box 22)
    - Personal financial information, including charitable giving expenses,1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - People Files, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Alphabetical by last name, A-C, 23 folders (Box 22)
  - People Files,1991, continued (Box 23)
    - Alphabetical by last name, A, C-H, 54 folders (Box 23)
  - SR17-International Files from 3rd Floor (Box 23)
    - Smithsonian Council Meetings,1991, 4 folders (Box 23)
    - 1988 Tax materials, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - SR 17, continued (Box 24)
    - DG Stock Info/Johnson and Lemon,1989 (Box 24)
    - USN Interoffice (Box 24)
    - Manuscript: Rude Awakenings (Box 24)
    - Africa Project, binder and 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Inaugurations, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - NED-National Endowment for Democracy, 4 folders (Box 24)
    - Pat (Patricia) Flynn Investment, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Plastic box (Box 24)
    [materials continued in boxes 29 and 34]
    - Printed material (Box 24)
    - IISS Speech (Box 24)
    - National Committee-US-China Relations, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Phone log1988 July 1-1988 December 15 (Box 24)
    - 1992 June 6-1992 June 13: Tokyo (Box 24)
    - Personal Financial Information (Box 24)
    - Ted Slafsky Recommendation (Box 24)
  - [Box #12, No SR number]--White House Documents; Baldwin Wallace College; Citation, Cape (continued) (Box 25)
    - Bob Merry (Box 25)
    - Michael Lerner (Box 25)
    - Kennan--DG (Box 25)
    - [Unfoldered Material: Judicial decisions] (Box 25)
    - [Untitled folder: Questions for Tom Friedman] (Box 25)
    - Rothwax (Box 25)
    - Hasselbauch (Box 25)
    - [Unfoldered Material: Hate Groups] (Box 25)
    - Economic Polarization article (Box 25)
    - James Fallows interview (Box 25)
    - Goldhagen, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Kennan (Box 25)
    - [Unfoldered Material: Notes on Movies] (Box 25)
  - SR-36, Editorials1990-1991 (Box 25)
    - DG Editorial, April 1,1991, Technology (Box 25)
    - DG Editorial, March 11, 1991, Hate Press (Box 25)
    - China Editorial (Box 25)
    - 13--One Week (Box 25)
    - DG Editorial, US-Mexico Trade: 1991 April 29 (Box 25)
    - DG Editorial--cont. China editorial: 1991 May 27 (Box 25)
    - DG Tomorrow--Education, 1991 June 3 (Box 25)
    - China Editorial, 1991 May 27, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - 1 Edit BBA (Box 25)
    - Divided Gov. (Box 25)
    - Media/Recession: 1992 January 13, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - 11 Edit, Two Nations, Rodney King (Box 25)
    - DG Editorials, 13 TMW, Detroit Big 3: May 13 Tomorrow (Box 25)
    - DG Outside Editorials: Washington Post: 1991 April 28 Outlook (Box 25)
    - Editorial, Gas Taxes, 1990 September 3 (Box 25)
    - DG Editorial, 1990 August 27, Gasoline Tax (Box 25)
    - China Editorial (Box 25)
    - Family Leave, Extra Material (Box 25)
      (from Box 26)
  - SR-36, Editorials1990-1991 (cont.) (Box 26)
    - China editorial (Box 26)
    - DG Editorial, 1990 December 31, issue: Good News (Box 26)
    - DG Commentary, NPR--1990 December 17: Minority Schol'ships (Box 26)
    - DG Editorials, 1990 December 10th, Tomorrow: Demo. Fall-off (Box 26)
    - DG Editorials, 1990 Octomber 1, (Wake-Up Congress) (Box 26)
    - DG Editorials, 1990 September 24, (Barbarities/Hussein) (Box 26)
    - DG Editorials, LA Times, 1991 January 26 (Box 26)
    - DG Editorial: Source File--1991 Feburary 11 Editorial: Mil. (Box 26)
    - DG Editorials, 1991 Febuary 11 New Heroes (Box 26)
    - DG Tomorrow, Tomorrow Page, 1991 Febuary 4 (Box 26)
    - DG Columns, 1991 April 8, Tomorrow Page (Box 26)
    - DG Editorials, 1991 January 21 Tomorrow, Gulf and Congress (Box 26)
    - DG Tomorrow, 1991 January 14,Bush's Hidden Stren[gth?] (Box 26)
    - DG Editorials, 1991 January 28 One Week, America at War (Box 26)
    - DG 6 Edit (Box 26)
    - 1991 December 9, Shun Isolationism (Box 26)
    - Democrats/Ideas, 1991 December 23 (Box 26)
    - 6 Pol Thurow (Box 26)
    - Source File #1 (Box 26)
    - Source File #2 (Box 26)
    - Source File #3 (Box 26)
    - Family Leave, Extra Material (Box 26)
    - [29 Pol] (Box 26)
    - Campaign 92, 1992 September 21, Gergen Commentary, Message to Job Seekers: Good Luck (Box 26)
    - DG 17 Edit,1992 August 17, Don't CountBush Out (Box 26)
    - 24 Pol Baker's Return (Box 26)
    - Clinton 13 Pol (Box 26)
    - 3 Pol (Box 26)
    - DG Perot--June 15 (Box 26)
    - Mark Shields audiocassette 6-13 (Box 26)
  - [Box #6] DRG Speeches1990-1991 (Box 26)
    - Black Man in America (Box 26)
    - Bennett--1 Yr. Later (Box 26)
    - DG Speech, Center for Nat'l Policy, 1990 Octomber 3rd (Box 26)
    - DG Speeches, Chicago and Boston: 1990 Octomber 28 (USN) (Box 26)
    - DG Commentary--WMAL 1990 December 17, Charitable Organizations (Box 26)
    - Colorado Springs, Air Force Acad. Spch., 1991 March 11 (Box 26)
    - Commencement Addresses (Box 26)
    - DG Speech, Coverage of the Middle East--Source (Box 26)
    - Georgetown Univ./Balt. Speech, 1990 Octomber 2 (Box 26)
    - Grad. School Speech (Box 26)
    - IBM Speech--1990 June 28, (Armonk) (Box 26)
    - IISS Speech, Background Info./Homestead (Box 26)
    - IISS Speech, Drafts/Copies of Speech, 3 folders (Box 26)
    - IISS File (Box 26)
    - IISS Speech, Other Speeches Given (Box 26)
    - IISS Speech, Source Files, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - SR 37 (Box 27)
    - Nat'l Committee on US-China Relations (Box 27)
    - Nat'l Committee on US-China Relations - Board of Directors Meeting,1991 September 27 (Box 27)
    - Mead - Exec Conf.,1991 (Box 27)
    - US-Japan Relations,1991 February 21-1991 February 22 (Box 27)
    - The Aspen Institute (Box 27)
    - World Economic Forum (Box 27)
    - Nat'l Endowment for Democracy - Board of Directors Meeting, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - Rethinking America's Security - American Assembly,1991 May 30-1991 June 2 (Box 27)
    - The International Media Fund - Exec Comm,1991 September 11, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - SR 42 (Box 27)
    - US Chamber of Commerce,1991 January 31 (Box 27)
    - Africa News Service (Box 27)
    - Africa Project - Rockefeller (Box 27)
    - AIDS/Media (Box 27)
    - American Assembly (Box 27)
    - America's Unmet Needs (Box 27)
    - Arms Control (Box 27)
    - Arms Sales (Box 27)
    - Auto Industry (Box 27)
    - Bilderberg (Box 27)
    - Bionomics Institute (Box 27)
    - Birth Rate (Box 27)
    - 1990 Budget Summit (Box 27)
    - Bureau of Census (Box 27)
    - Business Roundtable (Box 27)
    - Campaign Finance (Box 27)
    - Campaign1988 (Box 27)
  - SR 42, continued (Box 28)
    - Center for A New West (Box 28)
    - CFR Study Group (Box 28)
    - China (Box 28)
    - Children - Develop. (Box 28)
    - China - Policy (Box 28)
    - Competitiveness - US (Box 28)
    - Classi/Comp Society (Box 28)
    - Congress/Gulf War (Box 28)
    - Congressional Reform (Box 28)
    - Conservation Cultural (Box 28)
    - Cuba (Box 28)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box 28)
    - Defense (Box 28)
    - Journal of Democracy (Box 28)
    - DLC - Dem. Leader Council (Box 28)
    - Drug War (Box 28)
    - US-Financial Issues/Economy (Box 28)
    - Economy (Box 28)
    - Economy - Pacific (Box 28)
    - Elkus (Box 28)
    - Education, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - East Europe - Aspen Institute Berlin (Box 28)
    - Eastern Europe, 3 folders (Box 28)
  - SR 19 (Box 28)
    - Aspen Inst: Bd. Of Trustees (Box 28)
    - Aspen Group II, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Aspen Project III, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - SR 19, continued (Box 29)
    - Asia (Box 29)
    - Auto Industry (Box 29)
    - Balanced Budget AME (Box 29)
    - Banks (Box 29)
    - BCCI (Box 29)
    - Blacks (Box 29)
    - Blackstone Group (Box 29)
    - Bohemian Grove (Box 29)
    - Budget (Box 29)
    - Budget/Tax Cuts,1991-1992 (Box 29)
    - The Washington Campus - Board of Directors Meeting,1992 January 28 (Box 29)
    - Nat'l Endowment Democracy, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Aspen, Summer1992 (Box 29)
    - Blank Checks, cashed checks, deposit slips, 3 boxes (Box 29)
      (contain account numbers)
  - Plastic Box, continued from box 24 (Box 29)
    - National Commission on US-China Relations,1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - The Carnegie Endowment National Commission America and the New World,1992, binder and one folder (Box 29)
  - SR 32-Subject Files (Box 30)
    - Transition1988, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - 1992 (Box 30)
    - Japan (Box 30)
    - Asia/South Pacific (Box 30)
    - High Tech (Box 30)
    - Higher Education Program, Columbia University, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Terrorism (Box 30)
    - MacNeil-Lehrer Newshour1988 (Box 30)
    - International1989, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Newsletters
      - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 30)
      - American Political Report (Box 30)
      - Washington Intelligence (Box 30)
      - Sindlinger and Co. Research1989 (Box 30)
      - Polling Report (Box 30)
      - The Political Report (Box 30)
      - Kiplinger (Box 30)
      - Media Monitor (Box 30)
      - Janeway Newsletter (Box 30)
      - The GRC Cook Political Report (Box 30)
      - The Busby Papers (Box 30)
      - Mayo Clinic Health Letter (Box 30)
      - Greenberg-Zake Reports (Box 30)
      - Evans Novak Political Report (Box 30)
      - The Defense Monitor (Box 30)
    - Politics (Box 30)
    - Presidential Press Conference / Harvard, 4 folders (Box 30)
  - SR 32-Subject files, continued (Box 31)
    - JFKSchool/1988 Election, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Pamphlets (Box 31)
  - SR 46 (Box 31)
    - MacNeil Lehrer Retrospective (Box 31)
    - Advertising - USN (Box 31)
    - American Assembly (Box 31)
    - M/L Retrospective, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Center for the New West (Box 31)
    - Renaissance North (Box 31)
    - RAND (Box 31)
    - New School (Box 31)
    - SOS (Box 31)
    - Spain (Box 31)
    - ASNE Conference (Box 31)
    - Upenn / Ann Duffield (Box 31)
    - Wm and Mary1989 November 9-1989 November 11 (Box 31)
    - Thank you1990, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Thomas Jefferson High School (Box 31)
    - Trips - FGB (Box 31)
    - 92nd St. Y (Box 31)
    - The Washington Campus, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Institute for East-West Security Studies (Box 31)
    - Japan Trade (Box 31)
    - Joyce Foundation (Box 31)
    - Mark and Dave (Box 31)
    - Mark and Dave Show (Box 31)
    - Aspen - Summer1990 (Box 31)
    - Best of America Project (Box 31)
    - Annenberg Program (Box 31)
    - Institute of East West Business Dynamics (Box 31)
  - Personal Files (Box 32)
    - [Health Insurance materials] (Box 32)
    - GQ letter (Box 32)
    - Jewelry estimates (Box 32)
    - DG Christmas card list and info (Box 32)
    - DG Insurance (Box 32)
    - Gergen, Kenneth (Box 32)
    - Life Insurance Materials (Box 32)
    - Life Insurance (Box 32)
    - Disability insurance (Box 32)
    - Airline Information (Box 32)
    - Amex Membership Miles
      - American Airlines (Box 32)
      - America West Airlines (Box 32)
      - Continental Eastern, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Financial records
      - Letters (Box 32)
      - DG Investment transactions (Box 32)
      - *DG and Anne Joint Account Transaction (Box 32)
      - *Katherine Trust Transactions (Box 32)
      - *Christopher Trust Transactions (Box 32)
      - *DG IRA Transactions (Box 32)
      - *DG Account Stock Transactions (Box 32)
      - *DG Pension Plan Transactions (Box 32)
      - *file tabs list account numbers (Box 32)
      - Assessment J+L (Box 32)
      - Receipts (Box 32)
      - [Financial Statements] for meeting with Al Bergner (Box 32)
  - Subject Files (Box 32)
    - Aspen Inst. Dist. Fellows (Box 32)
    - Aspen Institute (Box 32)
    - AEI Election Watch (Box 32)
    - American Poli Sci Assn. (Box 32)
    - Aspen / George Wills (Box 32)
    - Lexis-Nexis Search results (Box 32)
    - DG/DAD USN phone calls (Box 32)
    - American Assembly, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - American Assembly Chapter (Box 32)
    - Duke Gergen (Box 32)
  - F Street Club (Box 32)
    - M/L Contract (Box 32)
    - National Press Club (Box 32)
  - Printed material (Box 32)
    - A Vision of Change for America (Box 32)
    - Democratic National Convention1992 Official Proceedings (Box 32)
  - DG Personal Chron File,1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - DG Speeches: ABA Meetings,March 22, April 25 (Box 33)
  - Subject Files: Abortion, Aids, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Biographies, photos, and press pass, 4 folders (Box 33)
    (photographs)
  - [Unsent Christmas Cards] (Box 33)
  - [Frequent Flyer Information and travel receipts] (Box 33)
  - DG Private-Computer Files1987-1990 plus directory (Box 33)
  - SR 16 (Box 33)
    - McNamara, Robert (Box 33)
    - Major, John (Box 33)
    - Masur, Sandy (Box 33)
    - Kerrey, Sen. Bob (Box 33)
    - Killian, Linda (Box 33)
    - Kissinger File (Box 33)
    - Kohl, Chancellor (Box 33)
    - Krasno, Richard (Box 33)
    - Ladd, Everett (Box 33)
    - Lance, Burt (Box 33)
    - Leftwich, Gail (Box 33)
    - Mitchell, Andrea (Box 33)
    - Mitchell, Sen. George (Box 33)
    - Mondale File (Box 33)
    - Morita, Akio (Box 33)
    - Moore, Sandy (Box 33)
    - Moynihan, Sen (Box 33)
    - Martin, Lynn, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Mathabane, Mark (Box 33)
    - Lippman (Box 33)
    - Lipsett, Marty (Box 33)
    - Lord, Winston (Box 33)
    - Lowenthal, Abe (Box 33)
    - Nixon (Box 33)
    - Nunn, Sen. Sam (Box 33)
    - Ottunu, Olare (Box 33)
    - Packwood (Box 33)
    - Perot, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Scowcroft, Brent (Box 33)
    - San Juan, Pedro (Box 33)
    - Solarz (Box 33)
    - Schlesinger, James (Box 33)
    - Schmidt, Helmet (Box 33)
    - Strasheim, Donald (Box 33)
    - Souter, David (Supreme Court Nominee) (Box 33)
    - Sununu, John (Box 33)
    - Sen. Roth, Bill (Box 33)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald (Box 33)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer (Box 33)
    - Saatchi (Box 33)
  - Plastic box, continued from box 29 (Box 34)
    - [Receipts and Correspondence], 3 folders (Box 34)
    - Christmas Cards,1989-1992, 10 folders (Box 34)
    - Printed material (Box 34)
    - Inaugural Notebook, binder (Box 34)
    - DG Phone Log,1988 January 4-1988 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Mondale Policy Forum (Box 34)
    - Smithsonian Council Meeting,1990, 3 folders (Box 34)
    - National Committee on US-China Relations,1992 (Box 34)
  - SR 16 cont. (Box 35)
    - Peterson, John (II) (Box 35)
    - Polin, Dan (Box 35)
    - Powell, Jody (Box 35)
    - Tsongas, Paul (Box 35)
    - Toch, Tom (Box 35)
    - Tutweiler, Margaret (Box 35)
    - Thomas Sowell clips (Box 35)
    - Tarnoff, Peter (CRF) (Box 35)
    - Thomas, Clarence (Box 35)
    - Reference Letters (Box 35)
    - Reid, Kathy (Box 35)